Hello, Carol.
This is a recording.
At the tone, you can leave a message
to request anything you might need.
We'll do our best to provide it.
Our feelings for you
haven't changed, Carol,
but after everything that's happened,
we just need a little space.
I need pump number one turned on.
Hello, Carol.
This is a recording.
At the tone, you can leave a message
to request anything you might need.
We'll do our best to provide it.
Our feelings for you
haven't changed, Carol,
but after everything that's happened,
we just need a little space.
I want a Gatorade.
The red one.
Fruit punch, I think it's called.
Real sugar,
not fake, and I want it ice-cold.
Hello, Carol.
This is a recording.
At the tone, you can leave a message
to request anything you might need.
We'll do our best to provide it.
Our feelings for you
haven't changed, Carol,
but after everything that's happened,
we just need a little space.
I didn't say tepid.
I didn't say lukewarm.
I didn't even just say cold.
I said ice-cold.
Do better next time.
Yeah.
It's the end of the world
As we know it
And I feel f...
I'm all right
Don't nobody worry 'bout me
You got to give me a fight...
Why don't you just let me be?
I'm all right, I'm all right
Don't nobody worry 'bout me
You got to give me a fight
Why don't you just let me be?
I'm all right
Head out on the highway
Looking for adventure
In whatever comes our way
And I know I gotta make it happen
Take the world in a love embrace
Fire all of your guns at once
And explode...
It's gettin' hot in here
So hot
So take off all your clothes
I am getting so hot
I wanna take my clothes off
It's gettin' hot in here
So take off all your clothes
I am getting so hot
I wanna take my clothes off
Georgia
The whole night through
With that old sweet song
Georgia's on my mind
I said Georgia
Georgia
Hello, Carol.
This is a recording.
At the tone, you can leave a message
to request anything you might need.
We'll do our best to provide it.
Our feelings for you
haven't changed, Carol,
but after everything that's happened,
we just need a little space.
I want to dine out tonight.
Someplace special.
I know you remember where Helen
and I had our anniversary, so there.
And, for the food...
Martha's Vineyard, 1999.
Helen's birthday, 2008.
Oh. Maritozzi.
And...
yes!
I'll give 'em this.
Those crazy bastards sure can cook.
The cat.
The cat is gray.
The cat...
Manousos.
We can give you a lift.
How about some water?
We're sure you don't want
to get dehydrated.
Losing just five percent
of your body's water content
could lead to fatigue and headaches.
Even kidney stones!
Well, we'll leave you to it.
There's a scenic viewpoint up ahead
that is particularly breathtaking.
It might be a good spot to rest.
You take care.
And if you need anything at all,
just wave to the sky.
Bye bye!
Yellow.
The dog.
The...
The dog...
is yellow.
Yellow.
The dog is...
yellow.
Yellow dog.
Dog yellow?
What was it?
The yellow dog.
...chases the gray cat.
Yellow...
The yellow dog chases the gray cat.
Monday.
Monday is today.
Tuesday is tomorrow.
Tuesday.
Monday is today.
Hola, Manousos.
- Hola, Manousos.
Hola.
The world is big.
Big the world?
The world is big?
The world is big.
Today, I am not going to the library.
Tomorrow, yes.
To the library, I will go.
Today, I'm not going to the library.
To whom do the coats belong?
The coats belong to them.
To whom... To whom...
To whom do the coats belong?
The coats belong to them.
The girl saves the mouse
from the trap.
The girl saves the mouse from the trap.
Manousos.
Please don't do this.
The Darién is too dangerous.
It's over 100 kilometers to Panama.
And there are no marked trails.
The forecast for this week
is not conducive to hiking.
It's going to be over 38 degrees
with 98 percent humidity.
And we don't mean to harp on hydration
but clean water is not going
to be easy to come by.
The tropical forest hosts a remarkable
diversity of snakes, spiders and insects
and many are quite venomous.
And then there are the chunga palms.
The spines can grow up
to twenty centimeters long
and they're covered in bacteria.
Even the smallest cut could lead
to a fatal infection.
Look around you.
All these items were left by people
who could carry them no farther.
Please, Manousos.
We can take you anywhere you want to go.
How about New Mexico?
Isn't that where you're going,
to visit Carol Sturka?
We could get you there by nightfall.
We can even transport your car.
We know how much it means to you.
Nothing...
on this planet
is yours.
Nothing.
You cannot give me anything,
because all that you have is stolen.
You...
don't belong here.
My name is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish to save the world.
My name is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish to save the world.
My name is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish to save the world.
My name is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish to save the world.
My name is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish to save the world.
My name is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish to save the world.
My name is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish to save the world.
My name is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish to save the world.
My name is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish to save the world.
My name...
is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish to save the world.
My name is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish to save the world.
My name is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish to save the world.
My name is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish to save the world.
My name is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish to save the world.
My name is Manousos Oviedo.
I am not one of them.
I wish...
Carol Sturka.